{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212622926","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212622926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 19ceccf1-d346-4578-9023-3625d0235959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wazo_lile-wazo-hayo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212647988","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212647988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walihisi_walihisi_walio_watu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212654885","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212654880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wanakijiji_wahalifu_wanakijiji_waligundua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212661762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212661759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walikutana_walikutana_wangu_wadogo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212668625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212668625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wakiwa_wakiwa_wanane_walianza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212675424","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212675424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wapenzi_wapenzi_waliamua_walio"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212682372","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212682367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walihisi_walimsikia_walihisi_wanawe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212689266","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212689266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wapinzani_wakiruka_wapinzani_wanane"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212696165","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212696165"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walitafuta_wakipiga_waliruka_walitafuta"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212703950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212703950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walitafuta_wakipiga_waliruka_walitafuta"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212715462","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212715461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walitafuta_wakipiga_waliruka_walitafuta"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212722488","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212722488"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_wachafu_waligundua_walioishi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212729391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212729391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima_wanawe_wakasema"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212737293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212737293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima_wanawe_wakasema"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212750609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212750609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 9bffe486-a973-494d-a961-b156a1448345"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima_wanawe_wakasema"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212775530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212775530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walihisi_walihisi_walio_watu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212782591","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212782590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wanakijiji_wahalifu_wanakijiji_waligundua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212789585","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212789585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walikutana_walikutana_wangu_wadogo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212796761","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212796761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wakiwa_wakiwa_wanane_walianza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212803722","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212803722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wapenzi_wapenzi_waliamua_walio"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212810813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212810813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walihisi_walimsikia_walihisi_wanawe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212817853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212817852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wapinzani_wakiruka_wapinzani_wanane"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212824998","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212824997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walitafuta_wakipiga_waliruka_walitafuta"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212832958","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212832958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walitafuta_wakipiga_waliruka_walitafuta"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212839948","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212839946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_wachafu_waligundua_walioishi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212856035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212856030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima_wanawe_wakasema"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212869417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212869416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" c2b3a7af-c062-4842-97e6-17e970612816"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima_wanawe_wakasema"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212916805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212916805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walihisi_walihisi_walio_watu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212924424","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212924424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wanakijiji_wahalifu_wanakijiji_waligundua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212932032","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212932032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walikutana_walikutana_wangu_wadogo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212939462","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212939462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wakiwa_wakiwa_wanane_walianza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212947031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212947031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wapenzi_wapenzi_waliamua_walio"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212954399","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212954399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walihisi_walimsikia_walihisi_wanawe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212964017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212964017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walihisi_walimsikia_walihisi_wanawe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212971467","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212971467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wapinzani_wakiruka_wapinzani_wanane"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212979037","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212979037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" walitafuta_wakipiga_waliruka_walitafuta"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212986380","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212986380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_wachafu_waligundua_walioishi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549212993624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549212993624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima_wanawe_wakasema"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.wa.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549213007955","data":{"timestamp":" 1549213007954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_195010"," gameId":" 78d74c7f-6575-4ca4-8939-edd2efd066dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.wa.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima_wanawe_wakasema"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}